<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on INZT</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on INZT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.136.5</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NextPersona</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/nextpersona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/nextpersona/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://np.smoono.com/&#34;&gt;NextPersona&lt;/a&gt; is a web application that enables its users to personalize their own digital “persona” and hold conversations with it natively. This application utilizes the large language model GPT-4 by OpenAI, enabling seamless and natural conversational exchanges in multiple languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NextPersona is developed in Python, with inspiration from &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/avrabyt/MemoryBot&#34;&gt;@avrabyt’s MemoryBot&lt;/a&gt;. Streamlit is chosen as the platform for frontend due to its easy-to-use GUI library and concise documentation. LangChain is utilized as the backend for this app for its capability of integrating multiple AI models, enabling the possibility of easy scaling and expansion in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPR System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/alpr-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/alpr-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Automated Licence Plate Recognition System (ALPR) is a machine-learning application that can recognize the text on vehicle license plates, from a give sample of image or video. An rigorous approach was taken to develop, train and optimize the models needed for this task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Specifically, YOLOv10 and YOLOv8 were adapted and customized to perform object recognition on licence plates. EasyOCR is adapted and trained to recognize and output plaintext from captured licence plates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScenicExplorer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/scenic-explorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/scenic-explorer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ScenicExplorer is an efficient mapping and navigation software that enables real-time interaction with all possible geographical data in OpenStreetMap format.
Written in C++, it is smart, user-friendly, and ultimately, does its job right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This application is developed as part of the design process for ECE297: Software Communication and Design, an rigorous course at the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of Toronto, in an industry-standard environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;auto-completion&#34;&gt;Auto-Completion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Searching for places can be a pain, especially when people just want to explore. Auto-completion removes the need for users to memorize every single place they intend to search up by bringing up suggestions instantly once the user starts typing into the search bar. Fast and responsive, the suggestions change dynamically as the input changes over time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
